var deck = [
  {
    "topic":"Music",
	"sequence":"1",
    "Question":"Which pop duo was the first western band to play in The Peoples Republic of China?",
    "choice_a":"Wham",
    "choice_b":"Simon and Garfunkel",
    "choice_c":"Chas and Dave",
    "choice_d":"Right Said Fred",
    "correct_answer":"A"
  },
  {
    "topic":"History",
	"sequence":"2",
    "Question":"Timber selected from how many fully grown oak trees were needed to build a large 3 decker Royal Navy battle ship in the 18th century?",
    "choice_a":"50",
    "choice_b":"500",
    "choice_c":"1,500",
    "choice_d":"3,500",
    "correct_answer":"D"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Sports",
	"sequence":"3",
    "Question":"Speed skating originated in which country?",
    "choice_a":"Russia",
    "choice_b":"Netherlands",
    "choice_c":"Canada",
    "choice_d":"Norway",
    "correct_answer":"B"
  },
  {
    "topic":"History",
	"sequence":"4",
    "Question":"Off the coast of which country did the Amoco Cadiz sink?",
    "choice_a":"South Africa",
    "choice_b":"France",
    "choice_c":"USA",
    "choice_d":"Spain",
    "correct_answer":"B"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Music",
	"sequence":"5",
    "Question":"The song 'An Englishman in New York' was about which man?",
    "choice_a":"Quentin Crisp",
    "choice_b":"Sting",
    "choice_c":"John Lennon",
    "choice_d":"Gordon Sumner",
    "correct_answer":"A"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Books",
	"sequence":"6",
    "Question":"In the book The Last Of The Mohicans what was the name of Chingachgook's only son?",
    "choice_a":"Mingo",
    "choice_b":"Lightfoot",
    "choice_c":"Magua",
    "choice_d":"Uncas",
    "correct_answer":"D"
  },
  {
    "topic":"History",
	"sequence":"7",
    "Question":"In which year did Louis Reard invent the bikini?",
    "choice_a":"1906",
    "choice_b":"1926",
    "choice_c":"1946",
    "choice_d":"1966",
    "correct_answer":"C"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Geography",
	"sequence":"8",
    "Question":"In which continent did the ostrich originate?",
    "choice_a":"Africa",
    "choice_b":"Australia",
    "choice_c":"North America",
    "choice_d":"Asia",
    "correct_answer":"A"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Books",
	"sequence":"9",
    "Question":"What are the names of the two main characters in Diana Gabaldon's highland saga novels?",
    "choice_a":"Jamie and Claire",
    "choice_b":"Fergus and Fiona",
    "choice_c":"Rab and Elizabeth",
    "choice_d":"Hamish and Maggie",
    "correct_answer":"A"
  },
  {
    "topic":"History",
	"sequence":"10",
    "Question":"Julius Caesar said 'The die is cast' after crossing which river?",
    "choice_a":"Danube",
    "choice_b":"Rubicon",
    "choice_c":"Thames",
    "choice_d":"Tiber",
    "correct_answer":"B"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Sports",
	"sequence":"11",
    "Question":"Who was the only English player to win the European Golden Boot award? ",
    "choice_a":"Robbie Fowler",
    "choice_b":"Michael Owen",
    "choice_c":"Gary Lineker",
    "choice_d":"Kevin Phillips",
    "correct_answer":"D"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Music",
	"sequence":"12",
    "Question":"Doris Day had a sleepy hit with which song?",
    "choice_a":"Pillow talk",
    "choice_b":"Golden slumbers",
    "choice_c":"The beds too big without you",
    "choice_d":"Tears on my pillow",
    "correct_answer":"A"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Music",
	"sequence":"13",
    "Question":"Which singer once took a bite out of a Beach Boys record during a press conference?",
    "choice_a":"Robbie Williams",
    "choice_b":"Engelbert Humperdinck",
    "choice_c":"Shane McGowan",
    "choice_d":"James Blunt",
    "correct_answer":"C"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Music",
	"sequence":"14",
    "Question":"Who was the first band to play at the Cavern Club?",
    "choice_a":"Swinging Blue Jeans",
    "choice_b":"The Merseysippi",
    "choice_c":"Beatles",
    "choice_d":"Merseybeats",
	"correct_answer":"B"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Science",
	"sequence":"15",
    "Question":"What are Lanthanides?",
    "choice_a":"Elements in the periodic table",
    "choice_b":"Mountains on Earth",
    "choice_c":"Mountains on the Moon",
    "choice_d":"Bacterium",
    "correct_answer":"A"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Music",
	"sequence":"16",
    "Question":"Which band was not from Liverpool?",
    "choice_a":"Searchers",
    "choice_b":"A Flock of Seagulls",
    "choice_c":"Stone the crows",
    "choice_d":"OMD",
    "correct_answer":"C"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Sports",
	"sequence":"17",
    "Question":"Which boxer twice defeated Nigel Benn in 1996?",
    "choice_a":"Thulani Malinga",
    "choice_b":"Steve Collins",
    "choice_c":"Roy Jones",
    "choice_d":"Gerald McClellan",
    "correct_answer":"B"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Sports",
	"sequence":"18",
    "Question":"On what make of motorcycle did Barry Sheene win the 500cc-world title in 1977?",
    "choice_a":"Kawasaki",
    "choice_b":"Suzuki",
    "choice_c":"Mitsubishi",
    "choice_d":"Yamaha",
    "correct_answer":"B"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Biology",
	"sequence":"19",
    "Question":"What part of the body does a turtle use to breathe?",
    "choice_a":"Belly",
    "choice_b":"Shell",
    "choice_c":"Mouth",
    "choice_d":"Anus",
    "correct_answer":"D"
  },
  {
    "topic":"Biology",
	"sequence":"20",
    "Question":"For how long is a dog pregnant?",
    "choice_a":"9 Weeks",
    "choice_b":"9 Days",
    "choice_c":"9 Months",
    "choice_d":"9 Fortnights",
    "correct_answer":"A"
  }
]